-Tell him. -Tell him.
-告诉他嘛… -对,就告诉他嘛
-Shut up. -Tell me what?
-闭嘴. -告诉我什么?
You won't look at him.
你看你,连正眼看他都不肯
I could use another reason why women won't look at me.
下回女人不看我时我有了新借口
All right. All right. Last night,I had a dream...
好吧,好吧,昨晚我梦见
...that you and I were
我和你
Doing it on this table.
在这桌上做爱
Excellent dream score.
梦中得分
Why would you dream that?
你怎会有这种梦?
More importantly...
最重要的是
...was I any good?
我棒吗?
Well,you were pretty damn good.
简直是棒极了
Interesting. In my dreams, I'm surprisingly inadequate.
真有意思,在我梦中我力不从心
Last night,you seemed to know your way around the table.
昨晚你在桌上表现神了
I love it when we share.
真高兴能与你们分享
You okay?
你没事吧?
I can't believe you two had sex in her dream.
我不敢相信你会在她梦中做爱
Sorry,it was a one-time thing.
抱歉,我只有一次
I was very drunk,and it was someone else's subconscious.
我醉得不醒人事,而且这是某人的潜意志
The One With The lck Factor
六人行 第1季 第22集 倒人胃口的约会
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Hello,Rachel.
好呀,瑞秋
Get off.
起来
Ooh,give me. Can you see me operating a drill press?
给我,你们能想像操作钻床的我吗?
I don't know. What are you wearing?
不知道,你当时穿什么?
Why would you want to?
不知道,你为何想操作钻床?
For short-term work. Till I get back my massage clients.
只是暂时的工作,直到我找回部份的按摩客户
Pirates again?
又是海盗?
No. Nothing like that.
没那回事
I'm just such a dummy.
我是个大笨蛋
I taught a "Massage Yourself at Home" workshop. And they are.
我教他们“自己在家动手作按摩” 结果他们就在家里作
Hey,Chan,she could work for you.
嗨,钱德,她可以为你工作
Thanks,Joey. That's a good idea.
谢了,乔伊,这是个好主意
I could. I could do it. What is it?
我可以,是什么工作?
My secretary's gonna be out. She's having one of her boobs reduced.
我秘书这几周无法来上班 她去动消乳手术
It's a whole big boob story.
一言难尽的波霸故事
-I could be a secretary. -I don't know if it'd be your thing...
-我可以当个秘书 -我不知你是否是这块料
... because it involves being normal for a large portion of the day.
-因为这份工作得要表现“正常”? -白天要尽量正常
I could do that.
我能办到
-What's that? -My new beeper.
-那是什么? -我的新BP机
Why does a paleontologist need a beeper?
古生物学家要那玩意儿干嘛?
Is it for dinosaur emergencies? Help. They're still extinct.
恐龙紧急事件?救命啊, 快来,他们还是绝种了
It's for when Carol goes into labor.
不,是为卡萝生产买的
All she has to do is dial 55-JlMBO.
她随时可以连络到我, 她只需拨个号码55-JIMB0
A cool number and a possible name for the kid.
这号码真酷还能当孩子的名字
-See you later. -Off to see young Ethan?
-各位回头见了 -去见伊森小子?
Thank you.
谢谢
How young is young Ethan? Young?
伊森到底有多小?很小?
He's our age.
年纪和我们差不多
When we were....
当我们还是…
-He's a senior in college. -College?
-他是大学四年级学生. -大学?
Rob that cradle.
这就是起源
He's smart and mature and grown-up.
他聪明,稳重和成熟
Mature and grown-up,he's a big boy.
稳重和成熟,他是个大男孩
This man-child has no problem with how old you are?
这位小朋友不在乎你的年纪?
No,of course not. It's not even an issue...
当然不在乎
... because I said I was 22.
因为我告诉他我22岁
-You what? -What?
-你什么? -什么?
-Oh,I can't pass for 22? -Well,maybe 25,26.
-我不像22岁? -25,26还说得过去
-I am 26. -There you go.
-我今年26. -那就对拉
Can you hear that?
听见没?
That'll stop when you pick up the phone.
拿起电话后就会停
-Oh,I'm on. -Okay.
-我来. -好吧
Mr. Bing's office.
宾先生办公室
-Sorry,he's in a meeting. -I'm not in a meeting.
-抱歉,他正在开会. -我没在开会我在…
Will he know what this is in reference to?
他知道这件事吗?
And he has your number?
他有你的号码?
I'll see that he gets the message. Bye-bye.
好,我会转告他的,再见
Ross says hi.
罗斯打来问候的
This is so fun. What do we do now?
真好玩.现在做什么?
Well,now I actually have to get to work.
现在我得开始工作了
"Most likely."
“没错”(Magicball显示)
Okay,I'm gonna be out there.
我出去一下
All right. Bye-bye.
好的,拜拜
Bye-bye.
拜拜
-Yes? -What you doing?
你在干吗?
Okay,windows are clean. Candles are lit.
窗户擦好了,蜡烛点上了
BeIt's too tight. Gotta change.
皮带太紧,我得去换一条
Did I turn the fish? Nope,because I made lasagna.
鱼翻过了没? 没,因为我做的是千层面
-Am I out of control? -Just a touch.
-我是否已走火人魔? -一点点
I don't understand. You've been dating this guy since...
我不懂.你们从他期中考…
... his midterms.
…开始约会
Why,all of a sudden, are you so...?
为什么,突然间你…
-What? -Could tonight be the night?
-我怎么了? -就在今夜?
I don't know. He's a great guy...
我不知道,他是个好男孩
...and I love being with him. But,you know...
我喜欢和他在一起,但是,很难说
...things happen when they happen. You don't plan these things.
事情会发生就是会发生,这种事无法事先计划好
-So,did you shave your legs? -Yeah.
-腿毛刮了没? -刮了
Would you let it go? It was just a dream.
罗斯,你就别再折磨自己了 这只是一场梦
It doesn't mean
不代表…
This is it. It's baby time!
时候到了,宝宝要出世了
All right,relax. Just relax. Be cool.
放轻松…冷静点
Yeah,hi. I was just beeped.
有人呼我
No,Andre is not here. Third time today.
不,安卓不在这儿,今天已是第三次了
Yes,I am sure.
对,我确定
I do not perform those kind of services.
没错,我不做那种服务
Services?
服务?
Oh,services.
哦,服务?
Yeah,you want 55-JUMBO.
对,你要打的是55-JUMB0
That's right.
没错
That's right. JUMBO with a "U," sir.
没错,有U的JUMB0
You don't want me.
不,先生,相信我你不会想要我的
Judging by his number, I'd be a huge disappointment.
从他的号码看来,你看到我会大失所望
Alrighty,bye-bye.
好吧,再见了
How was the first day?
第一天上班如何?
Excellent. Everyone was so,so nice.
太棒了,每个人都很棒
It pays to know the man who wears my shoes.
瞧,认识穿我鞋子的人是有代价的
Me.
我
-I didn't tell anyone I knew you. -Why?
-不,我没告诉任何人我认识你. -为什么?
Well,because,you know.
因为,你知道的
They don't like you.
他们并不喜欢你
-What? -I thought you knew.
-什么? -我以为你早知道
-Who doesn't like me? -Everyone.
-谁不喜欢我? -每个人
Except for....
除了…
No. Everyone.
不,每个人
-What are you talking about? -Don't feel bad.
-你说什么? -别难过
They used to like you a lot.
他们过去都很喜欢你
But you got promoted,and now you're Mr. Boss Man. Mr. Big.
自从你升职后,他们感觉你是上司
Mr. Bing. Boss Man Bing.
大人物,大老板
-I can't believe it. -Yeah. They even do you.
-我简直无法相信. -他们甚至还模仿你
They "do" me?
模仿我?
You know,like,okay:
对,比如这样
"Could that report be any later?"
报告要“何时”才能交来?
-I don't sound like that. -Yeah,you do.
-我没有那样. -你有的
"The hills are alive with the sound...
这山谷回荡着真善美的
...of music."
音乐
"My scone. My scone."
我的烤饼,“我”的烤饼!
I don't sound like that. That is so not true.
我没那样说话,这“不”是真的
That is so not That is so not
不是这样,不是这样
That Oh,shut up.
这不…闭嘴
-Did not. -Up until I was 9...
-不会吧. -告诉你,我到九岁时
... I thought "gunpoint" was a place where crimes happened.
还以为枪口就是犯罪现场
-How's that possible? -It's always on the news.
-怎么会. -新闻老是报导犯罪事件
"A man is being held up at Gunpoint."
某人在枪口下
"Tourists are terrorized at Gunpoint."
惊慌的观光客在枪口下
And I kept thinking, "Why do people continue to go there?"
我一直在想为何人总是要那儿去
I should go.
我该走了
-Unless -What?
-除非. -什么?
Unless you wanna stay over.
除非你要在这儿过夜
I mean,I'm going to. So....
我反正要在这里过夜…不如
Yeah,I'd really like that.
我也很想
Before we get into any staying-over stuff...
在我们考虑留宿的事宜之前
...there's something you should know.
我有些事情必须告诉你
Is this,like, "I have an early class tomorrow"...
这个就像,明天一早有课?
...or "I'm secretly married to a goat"?
还是你与山羊秘密结婚了
Well,it's somewhere in between.
在这两者之间
You see,in a strictly technical sense,of course,I'm not....
就严格的技术上而言,当然,我还没
Well,I mean,I haven't ever....
我是说,我还没有
Ethan?
伊森
Are you a virgin?
你是个处男?
If that's what you kids are calling it these days,then...
如果你们这些孩子,现在这样称呼的话
...yes,I am.
对,我是个处男
I mean,you're just such a good kisser I would never have known.
我是说,你确实是个很会接吻的家伙,我没想到
Well,I've excelled at every level I've been to,I just....
我在每一个级别都是是优秀,我只是
I just haven't been to that particular one yet.
我一直在等待梦中情人出现
I've kind of been waiting for the right person.
我一直在等待适合的人
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的? -真的
You do know I was talking about you,right?
你知道我是在指你吧?
Wow.
喔
You keep saying that.
你一直喔个不停
You know,you read about it. You see it in the movies.
书报杂志,电影上不断出现
Even when you practice it at home, man,oh,man...
甚至在家里练习
...it is nothing like that.
这感觉实在没得此
Listen,listen.
听着
You told me something that was really difficult for you.
你说你有些困扰
And I figure if you can be honest,then I can too.
如果你能坦白,我想我也能
Don't tell me I did it wrong.
别告诉我是我做错了
Nothing wrong about that.
不,那件事你没做错
Here goes.
我说了
I'm not 22.
我不是22岁
I'm 25...
我是25岁
...and 1 3 months.
又13个月
But I figure that shouldn't change anything.
我猜我们之间不会有任何改变
What does it matter how old we are? Basically,I'm nuts about you.
年龄根本就不是距离, 而且,我完全被你迷倒了
I knew after the first time we kissed. You didn't mention the Tic Tac.
我们第一次接吻就知道了,你没有提到“Tic Tac”
I just thought you were naturally minty.
我只是觉得你有一种自然的薄荷香
Listen...
听着
...as long as we're telling stuff...
在你坦承之际
... I have another one for you.
我也有话要说
I'm a little younger than I said.
我比你所知的年纪还小
-You're not a senior? -Oh,I'm a senior...
-你不是四年级? -我是四年级
...in high school.
高中
What we did was wrong.
我们错了
I just had sex with someone who wasn't alive during the bicentennial.
我竟和一个在建国两百年国庆 都还没出生的男人做爱
I just had sex.
我刚做爱了
Ethan,focus. How could you not tell me?
伊森,注意听,你为何不早告诉我
-You never said your age. -It's different.
-你也没告诉我你实际的年龄. -那不一样
My lie didn't make one of us a felon in 48 states.
我的谎言不会使我们成为罪犯
-What were you thinking? -I was too busy falling
-你到底在想什么? -我只是忙于
-Don't say it. -ln love with you.
-不要说. -爱上你
-Really? -Sorry.
-真的? -对不起
Well,fall out of it.
好吧,从里面出来吧
You shouldn't be here. It's a school night.
走吧,你不该来这儿的,你该在学校过夜的
Oh,God.
天啊
I'm like those women that you see...
我就像是那种…
...with shiny guys named Chad.
专门勾引小帅哥的女人
I'm Joan Collins.
我成了琼考琳丝
Who?
谁?
Andre should be there in about 45 minutes.
好,安卓再45分钟就会到
Yes,sir,the kimonos are extra.
是的,长官,和服很特别
Alrighty. Bye-bye.
好吧,再见
It's just easier that way.
这样省事多了
-You told me about the last dream. -No. Forget it.
-快,你已告诉我昨晚的梦 -不,死了这条心的
Why not? Was I doing something particularly saucy?
为什么?难道是梦中的我对你过于粗鲁
All right. Fine.
好吧
You were not the only one there.
不仅仅你在场
Joey was there too.
乔伊也在场
All right.
好的
Was there...
那
...anybody else there?
还有其他人吗?
You sure? Nobody...
真的?没有…
... handing out mints or anything?
…蠢蠢欲动的家伙?
No,it was just the three of us.
没有,只有我们三个
So was it you and Chandler...
是你跟钱德之后
...then you and me, or you,me and Chandler?
再跟我,还是我们三个同时?
-You know what? -What?
-你知道吗? -什么?
There were times...
有几次…
...when it wasn't even me.
…甚至没有我
That is so sweet,you guys.
真好,伙计们
Mon,Ethan called again.
摩尼卡,伊森又来电了
-What? -Ethan called again.
-什么? -伊森又来电了
-You're not seeing him anymore? -No.
-你不想再见到他了? -不想
Sometimes,things don't work out.
对,有些事是无法勉强的
This has nothing to do with him needing a note to get out of gym?
这跟他需要假条才能离开学校无关?
I did not say anything. I swear.
我什么都没说,我发誓
-He stopped by. -Next time you talk to him...
-他只是顺路过来. -下回见到他时
...could you ask him which one the strongest Power Ranger is?
能问闪电侠中最强的是谁?
Oh,my life is just so amusing. Can we drop it now?
我的生活简直是太多采多姿了 可以换个话题吗?
Sorry.
对不起
"It's morphin'time."
吗啡时间到了
-Stegosaurus. -Tyrannosaurus.
-暴龙! -剑龙!
I gotta go.
我得走了
Head rush.
哇哦,脑充血
One more,and then I have to go.
再一回我就得走了
Cool.
酷
Where you going?
你要上哪儿去?
A birthday party with some work people.
我要和同事去参加生日会
Work people? Nobody told me.
同事?没人跟我说?
I know. That's part of the whole...
我知道,他们中的一部分…
...them-not-liking-you extravaganza.
…不希望你大驾光临
A month ago, these people were my friends.
一个月前他们是我朋友
I'm in charge, but I'm not a different person.
当上主管并不代表我会变
Then come,hang out. Let them see what a great guy you still are.
那么说你今晚该来,和他们多相处 让他们知道你还是个大好人
-You think I should? -I really do.
-你真的认为我该去? -对,你该去
But could we not go together?
我们能不一起去吗
I don't wanna be the geek who invited the boss.
我不想成为邀请上司的家伙
-Hey,you okay? -Yeah.
-嗨,你怎么样? -是的
-This can't be easy for him either. -I know.
-这对他来说也并不容易. -我知道
This may take some time for him to get over it...
也许他需要一些时间来度过这个
... but,then at four, Muppet Babies is on.
但是,四点闪电侠就要开始了
Go deep. Deep. Deep.
更深点,深点,深点
Sorry,Shelly.
对不起,雪莉
See,with the fun?
看到没有,很开心?
Last night was great.
昨晚真是太棒了
The karaoke thing? Tracy and I doing "Ebony and lvory."
卡拉0K,我和崔西合唱了首“乌木与象牙”
You were great. But they still made fun of you.
你表现得很好,大家仍然取笑你
-What? -Now you're Mr. Caring Boss.
-什么? -你现在成了“管家婆”上司
Mr. I'm-one-of-you Boss.
“我要你”上司
Mr. I-wanna-be-your-buddy Boss Man Bing.
“称兄道弟”上司
Then I don't get it.
我更迷糊了
You know what? I think you just gotta face it.
钱德,你得面对现实
You're the guy in the big office.
你像个坐在大办室里的人一样
You're the one that hires and fires them.
有权录取他们,也有权开除他们
-They say you're a great boss. -They do?
-他们说你是个好上司. -是吗?
But they're not your friends anymore.
但是他们不再是你的朋友
-I just want -But you can't.
-我只是想. -你不能
But I just want
我只是想
Are you gonna?
不是要去…
Carol and I have a new system. If she punches in 9-1 -1...
卡萝和我有了新系统,如果打911
...she's having a baby. Otherwise,I just ignore it.
就代表她将生产,否则我就根本不理会
What about Andre?
安卓呢?
He got a call from our cousin,Nathan.
早上他接到我表弟纳森的电话
Frankly,it was a little more than I needed to know.
老实说我知道太多内幕了
That was gonna be my opener.
那也是我的开场白
Have you guys seen those new hand dryers in the bathroom?
你们看过浴室里的新吹风机没?
-I thought that was just a rumor. -True story.
-我以为那只是谣传.-千真万确
Look,I gotta tell you something.
我得和你谈谈
I'm not 1 7. I said that so you'd think I was vulnerable.
我不是17岁,我这样说 你才会认为我可爱惹人怜
I'm actually 30. I have a wife and a job. I'm your congressman.
其实我今年30,我有老婆和工作,我是国会议员
This is ridiculous. We're great together.
摩妮卡,这太荒谬了,我们在一起很开心
We can talk,make each other laugh,and the sex....
我们聊天说笑做爱
I have no frame of reference, but I thought that was great.
我虽然经验不多,但一切是那么美
-lt was. -Then what's the problem?
-的确是. -那么问题出在哪儿?
Ethan,it's....
伊森
It's icky.
经不起考验的
"lcky"?
“lcky”? 经不起考验?
You're actually gonna throw this away because it's "icky"?
因为如此你就想放弃?
This isn't easy for me either. I wish things were different.
我是不得已的,我希望情形不是这样
If you were older or I was younger...
如果你年长几岁,我年轻几岁
...or we lived in biblical times...
或是我们生活在圣经时代
-... I could really -No,don't say it.
-我就可以… -不要说
Love you.
爱你
-Are your hands still wet? -Moist.
-你的手还没干? -还是湿的
Let's dry them again.
那就再去烘一次
Or,like,"Could these margaritas be any stronger?"
这些萄葡酒能再烈一点吗?
Hey,Chandler.
钱德
Hello,Mr. Bing.
宾先生
Loved your Stevie Wonder last night.
我爱你昨晚的史提夫汪达
Thanks. About the weekly numbers,I'm gonna need them on my desk by 9:00.
谢谢.有关周数字的事 九点“之”前请送到我办公室来
-Sure. -No problem.
-好的. -没问题
You have to give them something.
总得给他们些话题嘛
That was Gerston,Santos,and who's the other guy?
刚刚是格斯顿,山托斯 留胡子的那个叫什么?
-Petrie. -Petrie. Right,okay.
-派崔. -派崔,对
Well,some people are gonna be working...
这周末有得有人
...this weekend.
…加班了
Oh,that's nice.
真好
Ross.
罗斯
I'm here.
我在这里
You are?
你在?
We were just....
我们在.
What?
什么?
-Great. Now I'm having a baby. -What?
-这下可好,我有宝宝了 -什么?
I'm having a baby. I'm having a
我有宝宝了.我有一个
-The phone,the phone. -I don't have the phone.
-电话,电话 -电话在哪儿?
I'm hurt.
我受伤了
Let's go. Come on,people. Woman in labor.
摩妮卡,快走各位快点,她要生了
-Look what I got going. -Save it for the cab.
-罗斯,看这是什么 -留着付计程车吧
We're going to a hospital.
你在干什么?我们要去医院
I can't look nice? There are doctors there.
我不能漂亮一点吗?那儿或许有医生
-Joey,get out of the fridge. -All right.
-乔,别翻冰箱了 -好吧
-What is that? -For the ride.
-那是干吗的? -路上吃的
-Like in a cab -Save it.
-比如坐车的时候 -留着吧
-Hating this. -Monica,come on. Let's go.
-真讨厌 -摩妮卡,快
Baby coming.
宝宝就要出世了
I can't believe I'm gonna be an aunt.
我真不敢相信,我快当姑姑了
-I'll have a nephew. -That's nice. Get out.
-我快有侄子了 -真感人,走吧
All right,I'm going. I'm going.
好的,我来啦,我来啦
Here we go. Come on.
走吧,赶紧